I love these kids because they inspire
me that make me that make me laugh
they're so funny they do these prayers
like they're like round as pull well is
exactly what you're worried about so
that's how you're supposed to do that
good job let it go we're with your now
they're like a scary song sing a scary
song daddy kids are so funny they stink
they want something scary they don't
know what's going I don't know what I'm
capable of you know I'm going to scare
them like I'm committed to that
opportunity if they're asking I think a
scary song my mouth scary fun at the
hilton pool the other day girl Kim guy
you know I'm a song
oh yeah scary song mattify I know I was
like that was gross I know so that lets
just took it from a G to like a g7 okay
however that one's I don't know what sg7
is but yeah so they're like scary stuff
and as a dad your goal is to sing as
scary and up top but they're not gonna
ask again you know you know I mean you
you want them to be fun but you also
want to scare them into downloading it
so I'm like I'm doing this curious kids
song I could think of like but he's into
who says that they may be right here I
just say something strange
listen dude we'll do it either way he's
losers for we remove the tolerance on
him strain and a dad hug not annoyed
that it is not scary
you know scary sound scary a song I
could think of for my kids was one when
I was in high school I thought if I ever
have kids this would be an interesting
song the thing to them it was a bad idea
that choice but I went for it because
I'm committed to the bed super Metallica
bad idea
[Music]
want to hear the rest of the joke click
the play button to continue watching